(Raj:)This says you can make
"end of life" decisions for me.
(Sheldon:)As your friend, let's hope it
doesn't come to that.
(Sheldon:)Please sign.
(Raj:)Did you sign this?
(Leonard:)There's a reciprocity
clause.
(Leonard:)You get to pull
the plug on him, too.
(Raj:)Well, that seems fair.
(Sheldon:)Congratulations and welcome
temporarily aboard.
(Sheldon:)Here's your I.D. card,
(Sheldon:)your key and your lapel pin.
(Sheldon:)Which Leonard was
too cool to wear.
(Sheldon:)FYI, part of your
responsibilities
(Sheldon:)as roommate pro tem
will be to drive me
(Sheldon:)to and from work, the comic book
store, the barbershop
(Sheldon:)and the park for one hour every
other Sunday for fresh air.
(Leonard:)Bring a ball or a Frisbee,
(Leonard:)you know, something
he can chase.
(Sheldon:)Also, you're tasked
with bringing home
(Sheldon:)all takeout dinners.
(Sheldon:)Tonight is Thai food.
(Sheldon:)You'll find the standard order
in appendix B